const quizQuestions = [
    
    {
      question: "Which king asked God for wisdom instead of wealth or a long life?",
      options: ["David", "Solomon", "Saul"],
      answer: "Solomon",
    },
    
    {
      question: "Which biblical figure endured great suffering but maintained faith?",
      options: ["Job", "Joseph", "Elijah"],
      answer: "Job",
    },
    
    {
      question: "Who succeeded Elijah and performed many miracles?",
      options: ["Elisha", "Samuel", "Nathan"],
      answer: "Elisha",
    },
    {
      question: "Which biblical book reflects on the meaning of life and human existence?",
      options: ["Psalms", "Ecclesiastes", "Proverbs"],
      answer: "Ecclesiastes",
    },
    {
      question: "Who was the devoted follower who first witnessed Jesus' resurrection?",
      options: ["Mary Magdalene", "Martha", "Mary, mother of Jesus"],
      answer: "Mary Magdalene",
    },
    
    {
      question: "Which Babylonian king was famous for prophetic dreams?",
      options: ["Nebuchadnezzar", "Belshazzar", "Darius"],
      answer: "Nebuchadnezzar",
    },
    {
      question: "What does the name 'Emmanuel' mean?",
      options: ["God is love", "God with us", "God is king"],
      answer: "God with us",
    },
    {
      question: "Which apostle doubted Jesus' resurrection until he saw Him?",
      options: ["Thomas", "Peter", "John"],
      answer: "Thomas",
    },
    {
      question: "Which prophet was taken to heaven in a fiery chariot?",
      options: ["Elijah", "Elisha", "Isaiah"],
      answer: "Elijah",
    },
    {
      question: "What is the meaning of the title 'Messiah'?",
      options: ["Savior", "Anointed One", "King"],
      answer: "Anointed One",
    },
    {
      question: "Who was Moses' brother and the first high priest of Israel?",
      options: ["Aaron", "Caleb", "Joshua"],
      answer: "Aaron",
    },
    {
      question: "Which gospel writer was a former tax collector?",
      options: ["Matthew", "Mark", "Luke"],
      answer: "Matthew",
    },
    {
      question: "Who interpreted dreams and rose to power in Egypt?",
      options: ["Joseph", "Daniel", "Samuel"],
      answer: "Joseph",
    },
    
  
    
    {
      question: "Who is called ‘God with us’ in the Bible?",
      options: ["Jesus", "Emmanuel", "Michael"],
      answer: "Emmanuel",
    },
    {
      question: "Who led the Israelites into the Promised Land after Moses?",
      options: ["Joshua", "Aaron", "Caleb"],
      answer: "Joshua",
    },
  
    
    
  ];
  
  export default quizQuestions;
  